JAEHYEONG JO

85, Hoegi-ro, Dongdaemun-gu, Seoul, 02455, Rep. of Korea

Email: harryjo97@kaist.ac.kr \lefthame: https://harryjo97.github.io/ \lefthame Github: /harryjo97

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest mainly focuses on understanding physical systems through the lens of graph-structured data and its geometric symmetries. In particular, I've been focusing on the generation of the graph with diffusion models and its applications to real-world tasks, e.g., drug discovery or protein design. My research interest includes Diffusion Generative Models and Geometric Deep Learning.

PREPRINTS

Preprint

DiffusionNAG: Task-guided Neural Architecture Generation with Diffusion Models

Sohyun An*, Hayeon Lee*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>, Seanie Lee, Sung Ju Hwang Preprint

Text-Conditioned Sampling Framework for Text-to-Image Generation with Masked Generative Models

Jaewoong Lee*, Sangwon Jang*, <u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>, Jaehong Yoon, Yunji Kim, Jin-Hwa Kim, Jung-Woo Ha, Sung Ju Hwang

Graph Generation with Destination-Driven Diffusion Mixture

Jaehyeong Jo*, Dongki Kim*, Sung Ju Hwang

Machine Learning for Drug Discovery Workshop at International Conference on Learning Representations (MLDD Workshop @ ICLR), 2023

CONFERENCE PUBLICATIONS

Exploring Chemical Space with Score-based Out-of-distribution Generation

Seul Lee, Jaehyeong Jo, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2023

Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the System of Stochastic Differential Equations

Jaehyeong Jo*, Seul Lee*, Sung Ju Hwang

International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022

Edge Representation Learning with Hypergraphs

<u>Jaehyeong Jo</u>*, Jinheon Baek*, Seul Lee*, Dongki Kim, Minki Kang, Sung Ju Hwang Neural Information Processing Systems (**NeurIPS**), 2021

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

MLAI (Machine Learning & Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Seoul, Korea

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Sung Ju Hwang)

Sep. 2021 - Present

· Conducting research on graph generative model with applications to drug discovery.

Kimlab, UofT Toronto, Canada

Visiting student (Host: Prof. Philip Kim)

Feb. 2023 - Feb. 2023

· Conducting research on protein generative model with diffusion models.

^{*} denotes equal contribution.

^{*} denotes equal contribution.

PAI (Probability Artificial Intelligence) Lab, KAIST

Research Assistant (Advisor: Prof. Ganguk Hwang)

Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021

Daejeon, Korea

· Conducted research on graphs (edge representation learning using hypergraph structure).

TALKS

Generation of Graph-Structured Data with Diffusion Models in University of Toronto (UofT)	Toronto, Canada Feb 2023
Score-based Generative Modeling of Graphs via the SDEs in LoGaG: Learning on Graphs and Geometry Reading Group	Online Oct. 2022
Learning with Graph Structure Data	Pohang, Korea
in Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH)	July 2022
Score-based Graph Generation for Material Design	Suwon, Korea
in Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT)	Jun. 2022

\mathbf{EI}

EDUCATION	
Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Ph.D. in Artificial Intelligence Advisor: Proffesor Sung Ju Hwang	Seoul, Korea Sep. 2021 - Present
Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) M.S. in Mathematical Sciences Advisor: Professor Ganguk Hwang	Daejeon, Korea Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2021
Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) B.S. in Mathematical Sciences Minor in Computer Science & Engineering GPA: 3.75/4.3	Daejeon, Korea Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2020

ACADEMIC SERVICES

Conference Reviewers

- · Learning on Graphs Conference (LoG), 2022
- · Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2022
- · International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2022, 2023